HIYAMA
（緋山）
I won't let you get away again.
我不會再讓你逃走了
How?
怎麼會？
This will be enough evidence to prove you killed Mr. Hanegi.
這衣服足以成為 你殺害羽木先生的證據
I wanted to find out.
我一直很想確認
Why Mr. Akizumi…
為什麼明墨律師…
got an acquittal for you.
要幫助你被判無罪
You're also connected…
你其實…
to the Itoi family murders from 12 years ago.
也跟12年前的糸井家滅門案有關聯
In exchange for getting acquitted of the murder,
明墨律師讓你殺人後無罪釋放
you do whatever Mr. Akizumi asks.
作為交換，你聽從他的指示行動
Isn't that right?
我沒說錯吧？
Please answer me.
請回答我
Come in.
請進
I'll clean them up right now.
我馬上整理
That file…
那份文件的內容…
documents what happened 12 years ago.
是關於12年前的案件
It was left by Ms. Reiko Momose,
是明墨律師的前同事
Mr. Akizumi's former colleague.
桃瀨禮子小姐所留下的
Momose?
桃瀨？
You want to learn…
你很想知道…
about Mr. Yusaku Shimizu, don't you?
志水裕策先生的事吧？
What do you mean…
什麼意思？
you've come to apologize?
你是來道歉的？
Mr. Akizumi?
明墨律師？
Your father…
你的父親…
Mr. Yusaku Shimizu…
志水裕策先生…
is innocent.
是無辜的
Are these all the documents she compiled about the Itoi family murders?
這全都是她整理的 糸井家滅門案相關資料？
Thank you.
謝謝
Ms. Momose was the first to suspect
最早發現的人是桃瀨小姐
that Mr. Shimizu was wrongly accused.
她發現志水先生或許是被冤枉的
But Mr. Shimizu had a compelling motive for committing murder.
但是他有非常充足的殺人動機
Embezzlement, right?
就是貪汙對吧？
Right.
是的
The Chiba Police suspected Mr. Shimizu and Mr. Itoi's involvement.
千葉縣警雖然懷疑 志水先生和糸井先生共謀犯案
But they couldn't find conclusive evidence.
卻找不到決定性的證據
Then Mr. Itoi was murdered by someone.
就在這個節骨眼 糸井先生被某人殺害
And suspicion fell on Mr. Shimizu.
因此嫌疑就落到了志水先生身上
The prefectural police found evidence
縣警在糸井先生的住家
of both their involvement in embezzlement at Mr. Itoi's house.
發現他與志水先生侵占錢財的證據
The prosecution began questioning Mr. Shimizu.
檢方開始對志水先生進行訊問
A prosecutor was assigned to the task,
當時的負責人
who was assisting at the time from the Saitama office.
就是從埼玉地檢署前來支援的
That prosecutor was Mr. Akizumi.
明墨先生
I was assigned…
我…
to question Mr. Shimizu.
當年負責訊問志水先生
Mr. Shimizu…
志水先生…
consistently denied committing the murder.
一直否認自己有殺人
At the time of the incident, he claimed he was at a park
他說事件發生的時候 在女兒的拜託下
searching for his daughter's stuffed bunny at her request.
前往公園尋找兔子布偶
But…
然而…
at the time…
當時的我…
I blindly trusted the prosecution's fairness.
盲目堅信檢方的正義
And I didn't doubt that he was the culprit.
深信他就是犯人
I didn't do it.
不是我做的
I was searching for a stuffed toy at a park during that time!
那段時間我在公園找布偶
A stuffed toy?
布偶？
You've said that dozens of times already.
那故事我已經聽幾十次了
Believe me.
請相信我
It's true.
是真的
I was really looking for it!
我當時真的是在找東西
You weren't looking for it.
你不是在找布偶
You were killing people!
而是下手殺人吧！
You had a dispute with the victim over the embezzlement.
你跟被害人 因為侵占財產的事而發生爭執
No.
不是的
Your wife at least thinks you did it.
至少你太太覺得是你幹的
A reporter gave me this picture.
這是記者給我的照片
Apparently, she left the house with your daughter.
她似乎帶著女兒搬出去了
It seems she's preparing for a divorce.
好像也在準備離婚事宜
With a five-year-old child,
她帶著五歲的孩子
being hounded by the media day in and day out…
每天被媒體記者追著跑
The poor thing.
真是可憐
I hope this doesn't emotionally scar your daughter.
希望你女兒內心不要留下陰影
S-Saya…
紗耶…
Whose fault do you think this is?!
你以為這是誰害的？
Are you going to keep causing pain to your family?!
你還想繼續折磨家人嗎？
I heard about your wife.
我聽說你太太的事情了
It was a traffic accident.
她遇上交通事故啊
Your daughter…
你女兒…
has been taken in by a children's home.
由兒童養護設施接手照顧
After moving, going through a divorce,
就在你太太搬了家、離了婚
and finding a job…
也找到了工作
Just when they were starting over.
新生活才正要起步的時候
They deserved…
她原本啊
a different life.
應該可以過上不同的人生
I did this…
是我不好
Could you say that again, clearly?
可以再更清楚地說一次嗎？
Who…
究竟是誰…
killed Mr. Itoi?
殺了糸井先生？
I…
是…
did it.
我做的
I compelled your father to confess to the crime.
是我逼你父親承認那項罪行
Given these reasons, I will now deliver the verdict.
我將基於上述理由宣布判決
The decision.
主文
The accused…
將被告…
is sentenced to death.
判處死刑
If you are dissatisfied with this verdict,
若是對此判決有異議
file an appeal with this courthouse within 14 days from tomorrow,
請於判決日的隔日起14天內
I'm the one who put your father…
讓你父親被判處死刑的人…
on death row.
就是我
I'm truly sorry.
非常抱歉
It was six years after the trial…
我是在審判結束的六年後
that I realized my mistake.
發現自己的罪孽
The one who informed me…
告訴我此事的
was someone you also knew well.
是你也很熟悉的那個人
Momose told me.
我從桃瀨那裡
That you…
聽說紗耶你
were at a dog shelter.
在狗狗中途之家
That day,
就在那天
when I met you and Cocoa.
我與你和可可相遇
I realized that I had taken away…
才驚覺自己竟然 從如此年幼的孩子身邊…
a beloved father from someone so young.
奪走她最重要的父親
Ms. Momose became aware that Mr. Shimizu might have been falsely accused
桃瀨小姐發現 志水先生可能是被冤枉的
and was continuing her investigations.
於是持續進行調查
However, she discovered she was ill and was unable to achieve her goal.
卻在此時發現患病 身體無法撐到最後
That's Ms. Momose.
那是桃瀨小姐
She passed away a long time ago.
她在很久之前就去世了
In the file that Ms. Momose entrusted to Mr. Akizumi,
桃瀨小姐交付給明墨律師的檔案裡
she wrote this.
這麼寫著
"An officer from the Chiba Police at the time,
“當時千葉縣警的警官
had found video footage proving Mr. Shimizu's alibi."
找到能證明 志水先生不在場的某部影片”
And the one who covered it up was…
刻意隱瞞那部影片的人是…
Answer me.
請告訴我
You unlawfully covered that up, didn't you?
你是不是用不正當手段 掩蓋了那件事？
Was it…
是我父親
my father?
對吧？
Your father…
是令尊…
and Mr. Datehara.
和伊達原先生
Carrying on Ms. Momose's wish,
明墨律師繼承桃瀨小姐的遺志
Mr. Akizumi attempted to look into the footage.
試圖調查影片的事情
However, despite having an ongoing case,
然而，他手上明明還有 正在進行的案件
he was abruptly ordered to transfer to the countryside.
卻突然被調派到郊外
Mr. Datehara must have intervened.
應該是伊達原先生搞的鬼吧
So, Mr. Akizumi is currently searching for this footage?
明墨律師現在在找那部影片？
One year ago,
在一年前
my mother back home passed away.
我住在鄉下的母親過世了
When I was in middle school, my dad died.
父親在我讀國中時就死了
After that, she raised me all by herself.
從那之後她一個人將我拉拔長大
Your mom's in critical condition?
你母親病危？
Whatever. Why don't you go, then?
是喔，那你回去吧
Thank you.
謝謝
You'll be fired, though.
相對的，你會被解僱喔
We don't need irresponsible people
像你這種中途丟下工作 沒責任感的人
who abandon their duties.
我們公司不需要
Looking back, I should've ignored him and gone anyway.
現在回想起來 只要無視他，趕過去就好了
But I was afraid of losing this job that I had finally secured
但那是我好不容易找到的正職工作
as a regular employee.
當下我怕被開除
That's why, despite the cruel treatment,
所以不管被多麼惡劣地對待
I gritted my teeth and kept working.
我還是咬緊牙關，默默工作
But…
不過…
Are you really talking back?
你還頂嘴？
How rude.
真討厭啊
Is this how you were raised?
是家庭教育出了問題嗎？
Did your mother not teach you anything?
你媽媽是怎麼教你的？
Well?
對了
Bring your mom sometime.
下次帶你媽來
Oh, my bad.
對喔，抱歉
She died, didn't she?
你媽死了吧？
Good thing she died, huh?
她死了真是幫了大忙
Now, you can keep working here forever.
這下你就能一直工作了
Take it back!
收回那句話！
Huh?
什麼？
How dare you insult my mom's death!
不許你侮辱我媽的死！
Take it back!
收回你的話！
Let go of me!
放開！
What the hell is this?
這什麼啊？
You'd better clean that up.
記得好好收拾
It'll get in the way of work.
不然會妨礙工作的
To celebrate me landing a job after college,
她為了祝賀我在大學畢業後找到工作
my mom bought this for me with the money she saved up.
用做兼職存下的錢買給我那支錶
Despite her poor health, she kept working.
我媽明明體弱多病，卻不停工作
She pushed herself hard to send me to college.
勉強送我上大學
Because she believed it would give me better job opportunities.
她說那樣我在將來 肯定能找到更好的工作
That's why I couldn't tell her about my failed job hunt.
所以求職不順的事我一直說不出口
When I lied and said I found a job,
當我騙她說找到工作時
Mom was overjoyed.
媽媽非常高興
But…
但是…
Her feelings were trampled upon.
她的那份心意被徹底踐踏了
I'll kill him.
我要殺了你
Next thing I realized, I was out of control.
回過神來，已經渾然忘我
I committed murder.
動手殺了人
I can't go back to being honest anymore.
“人生已經無法回到正軌了
I could die right then and there.
就算死在這裡也無所謂”
That's what I thought when…
我原本是這樣想的…
You have a visitor.
緋山先生，有人會見
-Get ready to come out. -Right.
-準備出牢房 -好的
Who's the visitor?
是誰要跟我見面？
An attorney.
是一名律師
Um…
那個…
Are you eating properly?
你有好好吃飯嗎？
Mr. Keita Hiyama.
緋山啓太先生
I've been looking for you for so long.
我一直在找你
Do you remember what happened 12 years ago?
你還記得12年前的事情嗎？
Perhaps I should clarify.
這樣說或許比較好
It's about the time you were taking jobs from Spilldoor.
就是你從斯皮路多爾 承接工作的那段時期
I'm looking for a certain video.
我正在尋找某部影片
I've come here because I figured you might know where to find it.
我想你說不定知道它的下落 所以前來找你
What's this about?
你在說什麼？
You used to live in Hanamigawa Ward, Chiba City, Chiba Prefecture 12 years ago.
12年前你住在千葉縣千葉市 花見川區對吧？
At a nearby park called Hishimi Park,
在那附近的菱美公園
a video secretly filming a woman was uploaded to the illegal site.
有女性被偷拍的影片 被上傳到非法網站上
Does this ring any bells?
你有印象嗎？
The illegal site?
非法網站？
After lying to my mom about getting a job,
我已經騙母親說找到工作了
I didn't want to add to her financial stress.
不想讓她再繼續為錢煩惱
That's when…
就在這時候
I was introduced.
有人將某人介紹給我
To a guy named Egoshi.
對方是一個叫江越的男子
There were tons of anonymous job listings on the illegal site.
網站上有許多匿名的工作委託
Like being a receiver for fraud
像是去當詐騙車手
and handling illegal drugs.
幫忙保管違法藥物等
There were even postings for disposing of a dead body
甚至有請人幫忙處理遺體的委託
and other things as well.
此外還有很多
Don't worry.
別擔心…
The tasks are simple.
要做的事情很簡單
I'd heard there were some dangerous people behind Egoshi, but…
我聽說江越背後有很危險的靠山…
I was stupid.
我當時太蠢了
One of the tasks…
在那裡面
involved secretly taking videos.
也有偷拍的委託
And…
那時候…
when I was filming at a nearby park, I captured…
我在附近的公園偷拍的影片中 拍攝到的人就是…
Mr. Yusaku Shimizu.
志水裕策先生
He's a condemned criminal convicted in the Itoi family murders.
他是糸井家滅門案中 被判有罪的死刑犯
The video was taken on March 4th, 2012, at around 7:30 p.m.
拍攝影片的時間是2012年3月4日
Around the same time as the Itoi family murders.
跟糸井家滅門案發生的時間相同
This implies that Mr. Shimizu was at an entirely different location
原本應該在那個時間點 殺害糸井一家的志水先生
at the time he was supposed to be committing murder at the Itoi home.
其實身在完全不同的地方
This video will be crucial evidence
那部影片能夠證明志水先生的清白
in proving Mr. Shimizu's innocence.
是無比重要的影片
Do you mean…
你的意思是…
It seems the video used to be on the illegal site.
那部影片似乎曾被上傳至非法網站上
It was found that the video was taken by a user called Kei.
然後他查出那部影片的拍攝者 是一名叫“啓”的使用者
And this user was…
而那個人就是…
I'm "Kei."
“啓”就是我
I filmed the video.
那影片確實是我拍的
But I can't help you.
但我無法協助你
Once I send Egoshi the videos I've taken, they're gone.
拍的影片傳給江越後就沒了
I don't have them anymore.
我手邊沒有
Who's Egoshi?
江越是什麼人？
Is he the administrator?
是管理者的名字嗎？
Yes.
是的
But I only met him once at the beginning.
但我只有最初見過他一次
I haven't been in touch with him since I quit.
不接工作之後就沒再聯絡了
Can you find this Egoshi?
那可以請你找出那位江越嗎？
Huh?
什麼？
I can't do that.
我辦不到
I've been arrested, you know.
我已經被逮捕了
Very well.
我明白了
From here on,
接下來
think very carefully before you answer.
請你認真想過再回答我
Mr. Hiyama.
緋山先生
Did you…
你…
commit murder?
是否殺了人？
I'll ask again.
我再問你一次
Did you…
你是否…
commit murder?
殺了人？
Mr. Akizumi secured your acquittal as he promised.
因為明墨律師依照約定 讓你無罪釋放
Is that why you're doing as he says?
所以你現在都聽從他的話？
No.
不
Once I locate the video…
找到影片之後
I intend to turn myself in.
我打算去自首
I've taken a life,
我曾奪走他人的性命
and I can never make amends for that.
不管怎麼贖罪都無法挽回
But…
但是…
If I don't take action…
如果我不展開行動
Mr. Shimizu might die any day.
志水先生不知何時會死
Despite what I've done…
就算是我這樣的人
if I can still help someone,
如果還能夠拯救他人的話
I want to do what I can.
我願意做任何事
So, they both know everything too?
所以他們兩人也都知道一切？
Yes.
是的
It all began with Hiyama.
關鍵在於緋山
You found a lead to secure a retrial for Mr. Shimizu.
你找到讓志水先生再審的契機
So, you started taking action.
因此展開行動
You exposed the corruption of those connected to the incident,
你揭發案件相關人
To make them admit that they…
是為了讓他們招供
took part in falsely accusing Mr. Shimizu.
是他們促成志水先生的冤罪
I'll assist as well.
我也會協助你
And I'll…
我也是
also do everything I can.
會盡全力幫忙的
But please promise me.
但請你發誓
That after this is over…
本案結束後…
you'll make Hiyama confess his crime.
你一定會讓緋山認罪
Of course.
那是當然的
I'll…
這個…
entrust this to you.
就交給明墨律師了
All right.
明白了
So,
所以…
does Mr. Shimizu want a retrial?
志水先生有意願再審嗎？
Despite insisting on his innocence,
他當時拚命訴說自己的清白
he was coerced into making a false confession.
卻被迫坦承犯案
It's no wonder he finds it hard to trust me.
他不會相信我吧
What about Ms. Saya?
紗耶小姐呢？
I've told her the truth.
我把真相告訴她了
But she didn't say anything.
但是她什麼都沒回答
I can never atone
我對那兩人所做的事
for what I've done to both of them.
即使贖罪也無法消除
Even so…
就算如此…
I'll reunite Mr. Shimizu with Saya,
我也一定要讓志水先生
no matter what.
回到紗耶身邊
Tsubasa Kamoi, huh?
“鴨井翼”啊？
Egoshi's contact information was no longer in use.
江越的電話號碼已經沒在使用了
However,
不過呢
when I reached out to the mailing list that was used during my illegal job days,
我依在非法打工時 使用的郵件清單聯絡別人
I managed to connect with someone who knew Egoshi.
結果裡頭有人知道江越的下落
It seems he's still operating in the shadows,
那傢伙依然躲藏在暗處
and is now involved in investment fraud.
現在正在做投資詐騙
Our priority now is to uncover Egoshi's true identity.
首先要查出江越的真實身分
But would he still have a video from 12 years ago?
但那是12年前的影片 他還會留著嗎？
He could use it as leverage to say, "You're an accomplice. Don't betray me."
他可以用來威脅我 “你也是共犯，不准出賣我”
So, I'm sure he's still holding onto the original data.
所以他肯定還留著原始影片
I've set up a trap for Egoshi.
我已經撒餌給認識江越的人了
I've informed an acquaintance of his about an easy target keen on investments.
我告訴他有個對投資很有興趣的肥羊
Egoshi should take the bait.
江越一定會上鉤的
Mr. Kamoi?
是鴨井先生嗎？
Yeah.
對
Give me your ID.
身分證借一下
This better be a safe investment.
這投資沒問題吧？
No worries.
別擔心…
I won't misuse it.
我不會拿去做壞事的
Let me jump right into the job details.
我馬上來跟你說明工作內容
Do you know about equity investment?
你知道股權投資嗎？
Yeah.
知道
I'm familiar with it.
我有聽說過
Put simply…
簡單來說…
That's Egoshi. I'm certain of it.
他是江越，絕對不會錯
No worries.
別擔心…
Follow my instructions, and I'll make things go well for you.
只要照我說的做 絕對會讓你賺大錢的
Right.
好
Bye then.
那我先走了
No worries.
你放心吧
Right.
好
I'll begin following him.
我開始跟蹤了
This investigation will take a few days.
調查會需要幾天的時間
Huh? What's the matter?
奇怪，怎麼了？
Are you hungry?
肚子餓了嗎？
What's wrong?
怎麼了啊？
Were you informed about Mr. Shimizu's case from the start?
志水先生的事件 你從一開始就聽說了嗎？
Well, I knew the basic details.
是啊，大致上有聽說
It's what motivated Mr. Akizumi to become an attorney, after all.
畢竟這是明墨先生成為律師的契機
Ms. Shiraki, what made you join this office?
白木小姐為什麼 會選擇這間事務所呢？
I think Mr. Akizumi has forgotten the reason too.
我想明墨律師肯定也已經忘記了吧
Ms. Saya, right?
你是紗耶小姐吧？
Come in.
請進
Mr. Akizumi will be here soon.
明墨律師很快就會回來
After that…
在那之後
I gave it a lot of thought.
我想了很多
To the point of driving myself crazy.
想到腦袋快瘋掉
Why did you remain silent for so long?
為什麼你一直不說？
You came to visit Cocoa.
你來見可可
You cared for her until she passed away.
疼愛牠到最後一刻
Whenever I faced difficulties…
當我遇上煩惱時
you were always there for me.
你總是來幫助我
Were you only nice to me…
但你之所以對我這麼好
because…
是出自…
you felt guilty?
你的罪惡感嗎？
I see.
這樣啊
You're right, Saya.
紗耶，你說得沒錯
This guilt will never fade away.
我心中的罪惡感不會消失
I was kind to you…
我對你好…
because of the guilt I had in my heart.
是因為我對你深感歉疚
But…
然而…
If there's anything I can do for you…
如果我能為你做點什麼
I want to do it.
我什麼都願意做
Honestly…
老實說…
I don't know how to feel about you.
我不曉得該怎麼看待你
But…
可是…
You're sure you can get an acquittal for him, right?
你絕對能讓我爸無罪吧？
I'm sure.
我保證
Let me see Dad.
讓我見爸爸吧
You should honestly ask him what you want to know.
只要坦率地問他想知道的事就行了
Yeah.
好
Saya.
紗耶
Please sit.
請坐
Ms. Saya…
紗耶小姐…
has a question for you.
有事想問你
You've grown.
你長大了呢
Dad…
爸爸
You didn't…
你沒有…
kill anyone?
殺任何人？
I didn't.
沒有
I…
我…
never killed anyone.
沒有殺害任何人
I did something wrong.
我確實做了壞事
I wrongly…
明知不可以…
stole company funds.
我卻把公司的錢給侵占了
It's shameful that such a bad person is your father.
如此糟糕的人渣 竟是你的父親，實在太丟人了
I thought…
我想說…
you'd be happier without a father like me.
沒有我這種父親，紗耶會過得更幸福
I'm sorry.
對不起
Because of my actions, you had a tough time.
是爸爸害你過得這麼艱辛
You've held on so well…
你真的很努力
all alone, for so long.
一直以來都是獨自一人
Are you serious?
這算什麼啊？
How could you say that?
別說得那麼簡單啊
That's such a foolish thing to say.
你是傻瓜嗎？說什麼傻話？
I'll decide what brings me happiness!
我怎樣會幸福由我自己決定！
Why did you leave me?
你為什麼要拋下我？
I never stopped believing you.
虧我一直相信著你
Because you confessed to the crime…
因為爸爸認罪…
It was more than tough for me!
我所承受的可不只有艱辛而已！
You left…
爸爸離開了
And Mom and Cocoa passed away too.
媽媽和可可也死了
I…
我…
was all alone…
無時無刻…
I was all alone all this time!
一直都感到寂寞！
The truth is…
其實我…
I didn't care if you were a criminal.
根本不在乎你是不是罪犯
I just wanted to be with you!
我只想跟爸爸永遠在一起！
Saya,
紗耶
I'm sorry.
對不起
Mr. Akizumi promised me
明墨律師答應我
he'd secure an acquittal for you.
會讓爸爸獲判無罪
It's okay.
沒問題的
I know he'll help you.
他一定會救你
It's going to be okay.
一切都會順利的
Mr. Akizumi.
明墨律師
I…
我…
I want to be with Saya and…
我想跟紗耶…
Mr. Shimizu.
志水先生
Let me…
請讓我…
prove…
證明…
your innocence.
你是無罪的
I uncovered Egoshi's identity during my recent investigation.
經過這幾天的調查 我查出江越的真實身分了
He lives in a high-rise apartment in Minato Ward with his wife and two sons.
他住在港區的公寓大廈 與妻子和兩個兒子同住
He's employed at Windom System.
任職公司是溫多姆系統公司
Egoshi is an alias.
“江越”是他的假名
His real name is Shuichi Goto, a 43-year-old UTokyo graduate.
本名是後藤秀一，43歲，畢業於東大
His public persona could work to our advantage.
他是有頭有臉的人物 對我們來說應該比較有利
If we threaten to expose his illegal business to his family or company…
只要威脅說會向家人和公司 暴露他的身分…
But first…
在那之前…
Look at this.
請看這個
That's where I live?
這是我家
This was taken yesterday.
這是昨天拍的照片
Prosecutor Kikuchi?
菊池檢座？
His presence there suggests…
他在這裡就表示…
They've uncovered the link between Mr. Hiyama and Mr. Shimizu?
他發現緋山先生 與志水先生間的關聯性了？
No doubt about it.
肯定沒錯
Have they also learned about Egoshi?
不會連江越的事情都曝光吧？
No, I didn't see Prosecutor Kikuchi near Egoshi.
不，江越周邊 並沒有發現菊池檢座的蹤跡
The fact that he's still monitoring Mr. Hiyama
他到現在都還在監視緋山先生
implies he hasn't gotten to Egoshi yet.
就表示他還沒查到江越那邊
So, Mr. Hiyama and Akamine,
所以緋山先生、赤峰
I want you to keep Kikuchi's eyes on you.
我希望你們能抓住菊池的目光
Come in.
請進
A visitor?
有訪客？
I don't have an appointment.
但我今天沒跟任何人有約
He's an attorney.
是一名律師
An attorney?
律師？
He said it concerns Egoshi's investment, and that you'd understand.
他說只要說是關於 “江越的投資”你就會知道了
If you're occupied,
他還說如果你很忙的話
he mentioned he'll be waiting on the sofa at Imperial Tokyo at 8 p.m. tonight.
會在今天晚上的八點 於東京帝國的沙發區等你
At 8 p.m…
晚上八點…
Let him know I'll be there.
請告訴他我會到場
He confirms he'll be present.
他表示明白了
Thank you.
謝謝
There's no movement.
沒有動靜呢
He's here.
他來了
Mr. Shuichi Goto.
後藤秀一先生
Or…
不
should I call you Mr. Egoshi?
還是稱呼你為江越先生吧
How do you know about the investment?
你怎麼知道投資的事？
I'm Akizumi, an attorney.
我是律師，敝姓明墨
I'm here on behalf of Mr. Keita Hiyama.
我是作為緋山啓太先生的 代理人來找你
Keita Hiyama?
緋山啓太？
I'll cut to the chase.
我就開門見山地說了
I want you to hand over
我希望你把12年前
every video Mr. Hiyama filmed 12 years ago.
緋山先生所拍攝的影片全數交出來
I don't quite follow.
我不懂你的意思
I've heard everything from Mr. Hiyama.
我已經從緋山先生那邊 聽說事情原委了
That he was secretly filming videos under your instructions.
他在你的指示下偷拍影片
Do you want to walk away?
這樣好嗎？
What do you want?
怎樣啦？
I simply wish to negotiate a deal with you.
我只是想來做個交易
That's all.
僅是如此
I'm not sure,
我不是很懂
but isn't the prescriptive period for secret filming three years?
但偷拍的追訴期不是三年嗎？
I'm impressed. You're well-informed.
你果然非常清楚
It's just knowledge. I have never--
這只是一般常識，並沒有…
Of course. I understand.
當然，我明白
You have your position to consider.
你有自己的立場要顧
I have no intention of acting against you personally.
我並沒有想對你個人做什麼
I just want to make a deal with you.
只是想跟你做個交易
Mr. Hiyama is afraid.
緋山先生很害怕
That you might use his past crimes
怕你會利用他過去犯下的罪行
to blackmail him.
進行恐嚇敲詐
That's why I'm asking you
所以我希望你能將緋山先生 過去參與偷拍的證據
If you comply,
如果你願意的話
we'll offer you fair compensation.
我們會準備相應的金額
Huh?
什麼？
Why would you do that?
為何做到這個份上？
In the world, there are matters that the law cannot resolve,
這世上有些事無法靠法律解決
and attorneys understand that.
律師很清楚這一點
Negotiating civil matters is just part of the business.
民事的交涉也是一門生意
If I possessed these videos,
假如我手上有那部影片
I could make money simply by handing them over to you.
只要交出去就能拿到錢
And since you're resorting to illegal methods,
再加上你們也採取了違法的手段
there's no risk of you reporting me.
所以我沒有被通報的風險
You really are a smart man.
你真的非常優秀呢
You catch on quickly.
理解得真快
I believe this deal offers no downsides for you.
我想這對你來說是沒有壞處的交易吧
And if I decline?
如果我拒絕的話呢？
You'll simply be ruined.
那只有你的人生會被毀掉
Not bad.
確實不賴
And yet…
話雖如此…
In business, speed is everything.
做生意要講求速度
I had a visitor before you,
有位客人搶在你前面
and I no longer possess that video.
那部影片已經不在我手上了
Excuse me.
不好意思
Yes.
是啊
Unfortunately, he didn't resort to intimidation.
很遺憾，我並沒有被威脅
What should I do?
我該怎麼做？
Thank you for your cooperation.
謝謝你的合作
Sure.
不客氣
They anticipated that you'd resort to intimidation to obtain the video, but…
我本來預期 你會用脅迫的手段來奪取影片
Shall we go?
我們走吧
Huh? Are we finished already?
什麼？就這樣結束？
If he didn't use intimidation, we can't have him arrested here.
沒有威脅你的話就不能當場逮捕他
Thank you, everyone.
各位，辛苦了
Too bad.
什麼嘛
I was hoping to see something fun.
我還以為能看到精彩的一幕呢
I see.
了解…
Well, of course, he isn't that foolish.
畢竟啊，他也沒那麼笨嘛
Good job.
辛苦囉
So, where were we?
然後我們說到哪了？
I've brought the public trial records from last week's rulings.
我把上週判決出爐的公審紀錄拿來了
Could you give them your approval?
請你審批
Do it for me, would you?
你代替我批閱就好了
What are you looking at?
你是在看什麼呢？
Me?
嗯？
Just some footage seized in connection to a case long ago.
在很久以前的案件中扣押的資料影片
Secret filming, how unforgivable!
偷拍這種事真是不可原諒！
There are many people in the world who engage in such acts.
這種人在世上多得要命
No matter how many you arrest,
不管怎麼抓、怎麼治
they still pop up like maggots.
還是如蛆蟲般不斷湧出來
FORMATTING
（格式化）
FORMAT COMPLETE
（格式化完成）
However…
不過…
Heaven…
老天爺…
sides with the righteous.
會站在正義的那一方
How about getting something sweet to eat?
去吃點甜食吧，好嗎？
Just as we feared, Chief Prosecutor Datehara
伊達原檢事正
located Egoshi before we could.
果然早我們一步找出江越了
Perhaps he acquired the video footage
他或許是用放過 江越所犯的罪行當成條件
in exchange for overlooking Egoshi's previous offenses.
來得到那部影片吧
He's here.
他來了
The attorney you mentioned.
就是你提到的律師
Yes.
是的
Imperial Tokyo lounge at 8 p.m.
晚上八點在東京帝國的等候廳
Very well.
收到
I'll dispatch plain-clothed officers right away,
我馬上派便衣刑警過去
and you as well.
你也過去吧
We were acting to divert Kikuchi's focus from Egoshi.
我們為了不讓菊池注意到江越 而採取的行動
But in reality, Datehara was playing us like fiddles.
反而讓我們落入伊達原的陷阱之中
The video has likely been erased.
影片恐怕已經被刪除了
We're up against the Chief Prosecutor, who holds information on criminals.
對方是檢事正，掌握著犯罪者的情報
While digging into Mr. Shimizu and Mr. Hiyama,
在調查志水先生和緋山先生時
he must have learned that--
就發現他是影片的拍攝者…
Huh? What's the matter, Mill?
什麼？米魯，怎麼了？
You keep this place quite tidy.
你把這裡弄得挺漂亮的嘛
Sorry about the sudden visit.
抱歉啊，突然來訪
I just realized I hadn't given any gift to celebrate
我想說過去的部下開了律師事務所
when my former subordinate opened his law office.
我竟然沒有來祝賀
So, I decided to drop by.
所以就來看一下
Here you go.
收下吧
Why, thank you.
真謝謝你
By the way,
話說回來
I heard you were pursuing a criminal who was secretly filming.
聽說你在追查以前的偷拍犯？
Why bother with something that won't even profit you?
為什麼要做那種不賺錢的事呢？
You ask, but are you really interested?
你聽了會有興趣嗎？
Good question.
這是個好問題
But you should be cautious about whom you choose to defend.
不過勸你還是考慮一下辯護的對象
Otherwise, your office might shut down.
不然事務所會倒閉喔
It must be challenging for the rest of you to follow this man.
你們要跟著他也很不容易呢
How about…
要不要…
switching to the prosecution?
改當檢察官算了？
You'll sweat for the country and its people and be thanked for it.
為國家、為市民揮汗努力 並受眾人感謝
Your lives would be stable, so you wouldn't have to worry about the future.
生活也很安定，不必擔心將來
It's a good job.
是很棒的工作喔
You're quite bold in your recruitment efforts.
你這是明目張膽的挖角呢
But I have no intention of handing them over.
但我不打算把他們讓給你
I ask you to leave.
你請回吧
I understand.
我知道啦
I'm busy too.
我也是很忙的
Well then, excuse me,
那就失陪了
Attorney Akizumi.
明墨律師
I hope this won't be the last time I address you as such,
我會祈禱這不是最後一次這樣稱呼你
He had a talent for being a prosecutor.
他有當檢察官的資質
He was a man who would do everything within his power
為了正確的判決，不畏犯錯
to secure the correct verdict, unafraid of making mistakes.
曾經是一個會盡己所能 拼命努力的男人
Akizumi was somewhat similar to me.
明墨跟我在某些地方很相像
That's why I can guess what he's thinking
所以他所想的事情
as if reading a book.
我再清楚不過了
He isn't cut out to be an attorney of justice.
他並不適合當正義的律師
Now,
這樣一來
the retrial for Mr. Shimizu will…
志水先生的再審…
You'll get to see him soon too, Mame.
小豆，你也很快就能見到他了
You have every right to experience more happiness!
你當然有權獲得更多的幸福！
Let's put an end to this for their sake.
這也是為了對方 就讓我們來結束一切吧
How dare you. She's my daughter!
開什麼玩笑？你把我女兒當成什麼？
I'm alive right now.
我現在還活著
Momose must have known.
桃瀨發現了
You'll be brought down soon too.
你也很快就會被擊潰
Give me a little more time.
請再給我一點時間
Don't mess with me!
少胡扯了！
We bear the same cross.
背負相同的十字架
Akizumi, save Mr. Shimizu.
明墨，拯救志水先生吧